Well, the Cowboys have added a new
addition to their defense their
defensive line room. Jonathan Bullard
first welcome to the Dallas Cowboys. How
you feeling so far? Thank you. I'm
excited. We're excited to have you. I
want to get started with you know,
obviously I read the story of you losing
your late grandmother Joyce Robs that
she passed in 2012. She was a Cowboys
fan. So it obviously means a little bit
more you being a Dallas Cowboy.
How would you describe what this
opportunity means for you? A kind of a
dream come true.
I grew up my whole family basically was
Cowboys fans.
My grandma was huge huge. That's where
it started obviously my mom everybody
but to be here and put a star on my
helmet
just means a little more knowing
what she did for me. So I'm excited
about it. When you look at what the new
pieces the new defensive coordinator and
Christian Parker and what Dallas is
trying to do with this defense.
What made the situation the best fit for
you at this stage of your career? I
think the defense that they're trying to
bring in is what I've done for the last
10 years.
I'm coming and be a big end be a
president on run downs
and and make it tough for them to run
the ball and try to get the running
defense going. So when I had the
opportunity to come here just fit.
I feel like that was what I was going to
lead to is you've been in a lot of three
four systems three four schemes before
excuse me. Sorry, but talk about you
know, what you feel like you add best
and value best at this point of your
career. I just think the smarts of the
game understanding what we're going to
get and being able to communicate down
the line with the guys which the guys
that's already there is older vets too
like Keanu and those guys. So I think
just us being able to communicate. I
think when you get older and you get
that experience the game slows down. So
it helps you recognize blockings and the
run plays that you're going to get. So
it helps all of us to be able to
communicate. So and then I'm going to
bring the toughness and the physicality
for sure. What has Christian Parker kind
of showed you what the vision is for
you? Have you had those conversations
with him just yet? No, I haven't gotten
to the whole vision thing with him yet.
Supposed to go meet with him soon after
this actually but I do know it's like a
big end position which I've did the last
basically 10 years I would say.
So I'm confident in what I can do at
that position. What are you excited to
most now being a Dallas Cowboy? What are
you looking forward to most?
Just the fans
my whole city is Cowboy fans too. So
that's been crazy ever since the news
came out. Just been able to go out and
put my stamp on on this season. We're
looking forward for you to put your
stamp on this season. Best of luck to
you and congratulations.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.